http://www.locfederal.com/privacy

CloseSee All
| ContractGeneral InformationAbout UsBranch & ATM LocationsWork For UsOpen an AccountMake an AppointmentContact UsMain Menu Personal
Apply For A Loan
Best in Market New and Used Auto Loan Rates as low as 1.49%.  Learn More
Mobile Deposit
Deposit checks from your office.
DocuSign
Need a loan?
Apply Online
Need help?
Get Support
Why LOC?
Skip a Pay
Did you know you can now make an appointment to see a member advisor?
Make An Appointment
PrivacyLink placeholder
Home > Privacy
Privacy PolicyOnline PrivacyYour EmailAdditional DetailsWe take guarding your privacy seriously.
Our obligation to our members is to keep your information secure and confidential.
You can learn more about LOC Federal Credit Union does with your personal information by reviewing our Privacy Policy.
Download Privacy Policy
Online Privacy Statement
As with any major website, LOC Federal tracks how visitors use our website in an effort to create the best online experience possible for you.  This may involve the use of cookies and tracking pixels, also commonly known as web beacons.
A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our website features or services may not function properly without cookies.
Tracking pixels usually work in conjunction with cookies and is a type of technology placed on a website or for the purpose of tracking activity. Like cookies, information collected by pixels is anonymous and does not include identifiable customer or personal information.
Cookies are safe, and there are no known cases of cookies being used to introduce or spread computer viruses. While a browser may save cookies to your hard drive, a cookie cannot be used to access your hard drive nor can they be used to reveal anything about you that you have not chosen to enter as a user on a site.
Through the use of cookies and tracking pixels, LOC Federal and its third-party advertising partners may collect information from visitors to our website, such as date and time of visit, IP addresses, demographic information, pages visited, the browser used, etc.  This type of information is used for analytical, measuring advertising effectiveness and troubleshooting purposes.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser to alert you of a cookie being offered or to reject all cookies. You can also turn cookies back on if your login is not recognized. Just go to the help function on your browser for complete instructions.
The Digital Advertising Alliance website contains important information on cookies, behavioral advertising, and what opting out will and will not do and choices you can make regarding interest-based advertisements. If you do not wish to have us and/or our third party advertising partners know which advertisements and subsequent websites you have viewed, you may opt-out at AboutAds (established by the Digital Advertising Alliance).
Your Email Address
LOC Federal Credit Union will never request that you send personal information via email unless you are using the Message Center feature in online or mobile banking. When you receive an email from LOC, it should use the @locfederal.com format, with the exception of eStatement notifications which use LOCFCU@email.mystatement.org .  We also do not sell your email address.
If you receive a suspicious email that says it's from LOC Federal Credit Union, do not respond, open any attachments or click on any links.  This is more likely than not an unauthorized attempt to gain access to your personal information for purposes of fraud or infect your computer with a virus or malware.
Protect yourself when using email
We may use the email you provide to us for marketing purposes, and you are able to unsubscribe from these emails if you wish.
Additional Details
Online Tools
In an effort to help you make decisions about your finances, LOC Federal may make available on our site financial tools, such as online calculators.  These tools are to be used for illustration purposes only, and we do not save the information you enter into them. Likewise, we do not make any guarantees as to the accuracy of the results when you use these tools.
Social Media
LOC Federal maintains a presence on social media sites.  You are encouraged to follow us on social media. Remember that any information you share is visible to all who participate on these sites, and you should never post, provide or send confidential information.  As with any third party site, the privacy policies may differ from LOC Federal’s, and you are encouraged to review them if you have concerns.
Third-Party Site Linking
For purposes of providing you additional products, services and consumer information, LOC Federal may partner with third-parties and link to their sites from locfederal.com.  Even though the site may be co-branded with the LOC Federal Credit Union logo, you should know that third-party sites may have different online security and privacy practices. When we provide a link to a third-party website, we will notify you that you are leaving a website under our direct control and subject to our policies.
Children’s Privacy Online
The information, products and services on locfederal.com are intended for audiences 13 and older, and we do not knowingly solicit, collect, or use personal information from children under 13.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Protect Yourself Online
Helpful tips to avoid becoming a victim of fraud.
Learn More
Don't become a victim
LOC offers a low-cost identity protection program powered by ID Protect®.
Learn more
Branch & ATMs
Find a Branch or ATM near you.
